[A Mission of the Heart]
[مهمة القلب]
[Episode 7]
[الحلقة 7]
Where is it?
أين هي؟
Are you looking for this?
هل تبحث عن هذا؟
My Lord,
سيدي
that belongs to me.
هذا يخصني.
Why do you have it?
لماذا لديك ذلك؟
It belongs to you?
هل هو ملك لك؟
How could a servant like you
كيف يمكن لخادم مثلك
afford such expensive jewelry?
هل تستطيعين شراء مثل هذه المجوهرات الباهظة الثمن؟
Someone gave it to me as a gift.
لقد أعطاني إياه شخص ما كهدية.
Qiulan,
تشيولان،
I'd hate to use force on a woman.
لا أحب أن أستخدم القوة على امرأة.
Would you rather confess
هل تفضل الاعتراف؟
or be tortured by me
أو أن أعذبك
till you spill the truth?
حتى تكشف الحقيقة؟
Tell me.
أخبرني.
What exactly happened that night?
ماذا حدث بالضبط في تلك الليلة؟
I meant to steal from Ms. Liu
كنت أقصد السرقة من السيدة ليو
so that I could pay off
حتى أتمكن من سدادها
my brother's gambling debts.
ديون أخي بسبب القمار.
When I
عندما انا
worked as Ms. Liu's maid,
عملت كخادمة للسيدة ليو،
I saw
لقد رأيت
where she placed her valuables.
حيث وضعت ممتلكاتها الثمينة.
That night,
في تلك الليلة،
my plan
خطتي
was to sneak into Ms. Liu room
كان من المقرر أن يتسلل إلى غرفة السيدة ليو
while she was out with Lord Chen.
بينما كانت خارجة مع اللورد تشين.
Stop it, My Lord.
اوقفها يا سيدي.
We haven't got in the room yet.
لم نصل إلى الغرفة بعد.
Why the rush?
لماذا التسرع؟
Oh, gorgeous.
أوه، رائع.
How can I wait anymore?
كيف يمكنني الانتظار بعد الآن؟
I've been dying to see you.
لقد كنت متشوقًا لرؤيتك.
Oh, My Lord.
يا سيدي.
Come on.
تعال.
Come on, give me a smile.
تعال، أعطني ابتسامة.
I attempted
لقد حاولت
to leave the room when Ms. Liu and Lord Chen
لمغادرة الغرفة عندما السيدة ليو واللورد تشين
fell sound asleep.
لقد نام نوما عميقا.
But unexpectedly...
ولكن بشكل غير متوقع...
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
What did you take?
ماذا أخذت؟
Please let me go, Ms. Liu!
من فضلك دعيني أذهب، السيدة ليو!
I didn't see anything!
لم أرى شيئا!
Seeing Liu Mei'er stop breathing,
رؤية ليو ماير يتوقف عن التنفس،
Qiulan dragged her onto the bed
سحبها تشيولان إلى السرير
to make people think Chen Zhao killed her.
لتجعل الناس يعتقدون أن تشين تشاو هو من قتلها.
It's exactly what we deduced earlier.
وهذا بالضبط ما استنتجناه سابقًا.
Has Chen Zhao's body been examined yet?
هل تم فحص جسد تشين تشاو حتى الآن؟
Yes.
نعم.
The coroner said
وقال الطبيب الشرعي
he died of a cardiac arrest
لقد توفي بسبب سكتة قلبية
caused by over excitement during sex.
بسبب الإثارة الزائدة أثناء ممارسة الجنس.
Anything unusual about the wine?
هل هناك أي شيء غير عادي في النبيذ؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
A small dose of ordinary aphrodisiac wouldn't be enough to kill.
جرعة صغيرة من المنشط الجنسي العادي لن تكون كافية للقتل.
Given all that,
ونظرا لكل ذلك،
the Ministry of Punishments can close the case now.
يمكن لوزارة العقوبات إغلاق القضية الآن.
I wish I could.
أتمنى لو أستطيع.
But my hunch keeps telling me
لكن حدسي يخبرني باستمرار
that Chen Zhao's death isn't as simple as it appears.
إن موت تشين تشاو ليس بهذه البساطة كما يبدو.
What makes you say that?
ما الذي يجعلك تقول ذلك؟
When Mrs. Chen came
عندما جاءت السيدة تشين
to claimed Chen Zhao's body,
للمطالبة بجثة تشين تشاو،
the expression on her face was rather peculiar.
وكان التعبير على وجهها غريبًا إلى حد ما.
Lord Shen,
اللورد شين،
I'm here
أنا هنا
to claim my husband's body.
للمطالبة بجثة زوجي.
Mao.
هذا كل شيء.
Yes.
نعم.
Thanks, Lord Shen.
شكرا لك يا سيد شين.
In theory,
من الناحية النظرية،
Mrs. Chen should've grieved,
كان ينبغي للسيدة تشين أن تحزن،
but I actually caught her smiling.
لكنني في الحقيقة رأيتها تبتسم.
She even personally came and checked
حتى أنها جاءت شخصيا وفحصت
if Chen Zhao was dead.
إذا كان تشين تشاو ميتًا.
Something must be off.
لابد أن يكون هناك خطأ ما.
It's a no-brainer.
إنه أمر لا يحتاج إلى تفكير.
I think there's a different cause of Chen Zhao's death.
أعتقد أن هناك سببًا مختلفًا لوفاة تشين تشاو.
Now that you're suspicious, just conduct an investigation.
الآن بعد أن أصبحت تشك، قم بإجراء تحقيق.
Why did you ask us to come?
لماذا طلبت منا أن نأتي؟
I didn't ask for you.
لم اسألك
The one I asked for was Yu.
الذي طلبته هو يو.
Yu,
يو،
would you join me in visiting the Chen Mansion at night?
هل يمكنك الانضمام إلي لزيارة قصر تشين في الليل؟
I guarantee
انا اضمن
there will be a handsome reward.
سيكون هناك مكافأة كبيرة.
I disagree.
أنا أعترض.
Who are you to make decisions for Yu?
من أنت لتتخذ القرارات نيابة عن يو؟
Why can't I do that?
لماذا لا أستطيع فعل ذلك؟
Don't you forget
لا تنسى
she works for the Imperial Guard now.
وهي تعمل في الحرس الإمبراطوري الآن.
You and I are both officials.
أنت وأنا مسؤولين.
We should help each other
ينبغي علينا أن نساعد بعضنا البعض
in the course of seeking the truth.
في سياق البحث عن الحقيقة.
Why draw clear boundaries?
لماذا نرسم حدود واضحة؟
Shen Pan,
شين بان،
are all the officers in the Ministry of Punishments dead now?
هل جميع الضباط في وزارة العقوبات ماتوا الآن؟
I'm determined to take Yu with me.
لقد قررت أن آخذ يو معي.
Then let's see if you're able to do that.
إذن دعنا نرى إذا كنت قادرًا على القيام بذلك.
Lu Zhan is a real punk.
لو تشان هو بانك حقيقي.
He kept hitting my face.
لقد واصل ضرب وجهي.
You big loser.
أنت الخاسر الكبير.
Lord Shen,
اللورد شين،
did your hands get hurt?
هل أصيبت يديك بالأذى؟
No.
لا.
That's good.
هذا جيد.
It was my face that got injured.
لقد كان وجهي هو الذي أصيب.
Yu, why did you ask about my hands?
يو لماذا سألت عن يدي؟
She's not worried about you,
إنها ليست قلقة عليك
but her money makers.
لكنها صانعة أموالها.
I'm just concerned about you, My Lord.
أنا فقط أشعر بالقلق عليك يا سيدي.
Lord Shen,
اللورد شين،
let me put salve on your face.
دعني أضع المرهم على وجهك.
Here.
هنا.
Does it hurt?
هل يؤلمك؟
Not much.
ليس كثيراً.
What is this about?
ما هذا؟
Don't you see I'm also injured?
ألا ترى أنني مصاب أيضًا؟
Why are you only treating him?
لماذا تعالجيه فقط؟
Those minor injuries of yours
تلك الإصابات الطفيفة التي تعرضت لها
are barely visible to the eye.
بالكاد يمكن رؤيتها بالعين.
Why even complain?
لماذا الشكوى أصلا؟
Treat them yourself.
تعامل معهم بنفسك.
I'm busy.
انا مشغول.
Hope to see you again soon, Mr. Wang. Bye.
أتمنى أن أراك قريبًا، سيد وانغ. مع السلامة.
Sir, it's been a while since your last visit.
سيدي، لقد مر وقت طويل منذ زيارتك الأخيرة.
Officer Huang
الضابط هوانغ
is really getting out of line.
لقد أصبح الأمر خارجا عن الخط حقا.
Does she even know who her superior is?
هل تعرف من هو رئيسها؟
Do you have to be this mad because she didn't
هل يجب أن تكون غاضبًا إلى هذا الحد لأنها لم تفعل ذلك؟
treat your injuries?
علاج إصاباتك؟
What do you know?
ماذا تعرف؟
I just hate to lose to Shen Pan.
أنا أكره الخسارة أمام شين بان.
And you...
وأنت...
I asked you to choose a place for drinks.
طلبت منك اختيار مكان للمشروبات.
What kind of place is this?
ما نوع هذا المكان؟
Sir...
سيد...
Look what a place you picked!
انظر ما هو المكان الذي اخترته!
My salary is way too low
راتبي منخفض جدًا
for this place.
لهذا المكان.
If you hadn't objected,
لو لم تعترض،
I would've got some girls to this table.
كنت سأحضر بعض الفتيات إلى هذه الطاولة.
But I'm fine with how it is now.
لكنني بخير مع الوضع الحالي.
What nonsense are you talking?
ما هذا الهراء الذي تتحدث عنه؟
All men should contribute to the court
يجب على جميع الرجال المساهمة في المحكمة
and make achievements.
وتحقيق الإنجازات.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
But in the matter about Officer Huang,
ولكن في مسألة الضابط هوانغ،
I have to say you did wrong.
يجب أن أقول أنك فعلت خطأ.
It was up to her to decide
كان الأمر متروكًا لها لتقرر
whether to assist Lord Shen or not.
سواء أكان ذلك لمساعدة اللورد شين أم لا.
Why did you try to make decisions for her?
لماذا حاولت اتخاذ القرارات نيابة عنها؟
Why couldn't I do that?
لماذا لم أستطع فعل ذلك؟
She's now working for the Imperial Guard, isn't she?
إنها تعمل الآن في الحرس الإمبراطوري، أليس كذلك؟
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
But you don't own her.
ولكنك لا تملكها.
You can't stop her from making money, can you?
لا يمكنك منعها من كسب المال، أليس كذلك؟
When it comes to winning a girl's heart,
عندما يتعلق الأمر بكسب قلب الفتاة،
Lord Shen does outperform you.
اللورد شين يتفوق عليك.
You should really learn from him.
ينبغي عليك حقا أن تتعلم منه.
Are you hearing yourself?
هل تسمع نفسك؟
You'll pay for this meal.
سوف تدفع ثمن هذه الوجبة.
My Lord,
سيدي
didn't you say this would be your treat?
ألم تقل أن هذه ستكون هديتك؟
I'm terribly sorry, sir.
أنا آسف جدًا يا سيدي.
Off you go.
إذهب بعيدا.
Hold on!
يتمسك!
What's the matter, sir?
ما الأمر يا سيدي؟
What kind of wine is this?
ما نوع هذا النبيذ؟
It's called "Drunken Dream."
يطلق عليه اسم "الحلم المخمور".
It nourishes kidneys, boosts virility,
يغذي الكلى ويعزز القدرة الجنسية.
and enhances pleasure.
ويعزز المتعة.
It's an exclusive specialty here.
إنه تخصص حصري هنا.
Are there varieties of this wine?
هل هناك أنواع من هذا النبيذ؟
Yes.
نعم.
Bring them all to me.
أحضرهم جميعا إلي.
Why aren't you moving yet?
لماذا لم تتحرك بعد؟
Yes, sir. I'll go get them.
نعم سيدي، سأذهب لأحضرهم.
Yu, have you eaten yet?
يو هل أكلت بعد؟
Yes, I have.
نعم لدي.
I came to see you for real business.
لقد جئت لرؤيتك من أجل عمل حقيقي.
What's this?
ما هذا؟
The money
المال
we earned for selling Lord Lu's portraits.
لقد حصلنا على المال من بيع صور اللورد لو.
Let's each keep half of it.
فليحتفظ كل منا بالنصف منه.
No need.
لا حاجة.
I promised to help you make money.
لقد وعدتك بأن أساعدك في كسب المال.
No way.
مستحيل.
How can you not get anything in return for your effort?
كيف لا تحصل على أي شيء في مقابل مجهودك؟
Please take it,
من فضلك خذها
or I'll be too embarrassed
أو سأشعر بالحرج الشديد
to ask you to be my business partner again.
لأطلب منك أن تكون شريكي التجاري مرة أخرى.
You want me to be your business partner again?
هل تريدني أن أكون شريكك التجاري مرة أخرى؟
Am I disturbing you, My Lord?
هل أزعجك يا سيدي؟
Not at all.
مُطْلَقاً.
It's just...
إنه فقط...
that others may think of me
حتى يفكر الآخرون بي
as a philanderer,
كزير نساء،
so they wouldn't fraternize with me.
حتى لا يتعاملوا معي بشكل ودي.
Do you not mind it at all?
هل لا يزعجك ذلك على الإطلاق؟
I don't think you're like what people say you are.
لا أعتقد أنك مثل ما يقول الناس عنك.
On the contrary,
على العكس تماما،
in my eyes, you truly respect women.
في عيني، أنت تحترم النساء حقًا.
You wouldn't look down on a female
لن تنظر بازدراء إلى أنثى
because of her background.
بسبب خلفيتها.
You've noticed that?
هل لاحظت ذلك؟
I learned of what Xue Jingshu did.
لقد علمت بما فعله Xue Jingshu.
Although she was a murderer,
على الرغم من أنها كانت قاتلة،
you still kept her
مازلت تحتفظ بها
from unjust treatment in prison.
من المعاملة غير العادلة في السجن.
You also had her body properly buried.
لقد دفنت جثتها بشكل صحيح أيضًا.
So many women
الكثير من النساء
were assaulted and abused when they were alive.
تعرضوا للاعتداء والإساءة عندما كانوا على قيد الحياة.
Their bodies were left in the wilderness after they died.
تركت جثثهم في البرية بعد وفاتهم.
Xue Jingshu was lucky
كان Xue Jingshu محظوظًا
to have met you, My Lord.
أن التقي بك يا سيدي.
You should keep all the money.
ينبغي عليك الاحتفاظ بكل الأموال.
I'll take it then.
سوف آخذه إذن.